I'm not going to your party.
我不会去你的派对的
I knew it!
我就知道
What? What could be so important that it's worth leading the bergen right to us?
到底怎么了 有什么能重要到 直接吸引博啃的注意也在所不惜
You don't know that. It could still be out there.
你怎么知道的 说不定还在
Watching. Waiting
盯着我们 等着我们
What? No.
什么 不愿意
They're your friends.
他们是你朋友才对
I'm staying right here in my bunker where it's safe.
我就好好待在我安全的堡垒里
Forever? No.
永远 怎么可能
Yeah...I really only have enough supplies down here to last me 10 years..
对 我在这里储备的物资 其实也就够我活十年
11 if I'm willing to store and drink my own sweat.
要是愿意保存汗液当水喝的话就十一年
Which I am.
而且我很愿意
You all said I was crazy, huh?
你们还都说我疯了是吧
Well, who's crazy now?
现在看看谁才疯了
Me. Crazy prepared.
就是我 疯狂级别未雨绸缪